[MUSIC PLAYING]
（音乐）
PAUL LEWIS: Hello, and welcome to this Supercharged TL;DW,
Paul Lewis：嗨，欢迎来到Supercharged TL； DW
the sort of beard-free version.
非胡须版
I don't know what happened to the hair.
我不知道头发怎么了
It just-- [SUCKING AND POPPING SOUND],
只是[拉动声音]
it abandoned me, like the stuff up there.
他像其他人一样离开了我
[GRUNTING]
[咕umble]
Well, last time, Surma and I took the router
好吧，我上次与Sarma搭路由器时
that we made two sessions ago and turned it
我们制作了两集并将其转化为
into a more advanced router.
更先进的路由器
Let me show you what we did.
让我告诉你我们做了什么
So you can see on screen, it's not
您可以在屏幕上观看
vastly different from last time, except that now we've
与上一个没有太大区别，但我们刚刚添加了
got this spinner, and then the content fades in.
该转子，然后使内部组件褪色
But actually, under the hood, a bunch of things have changed.
但实际上，在盖子下您会改变很多东西
Let's talk about that over there in Theory Corner.
让我们在理论角谈一下
[LAUGHTER] Hello, welcome to Theory Corner.
[笑声]您好，欢迎来到理论角
Good of you to join me.
我很高兴你加入了我
That's probably because I asked you to.
绝对是因为我问你
Don't worry about that.
不要打扰
Anyway, the router is pretty much the same
无论如何，路由器总体上是相似的
as last time, except last time, we
上一次，但是以前我们有
had one index page, which had all the content in.
一个索引页面，包含所有组件
And no matter which URL you went to,
这样您转到的任何URL
we served you the same index.
我们将为您提供相同的索引
No more.
现在不一样了
What we've done is we've broken each of these out
现在我们要做的是将这个碎片化
into their own individual pages.
到他们的个人页面
That means, when we deep link, we're
也就是说，当我们深入连接时
just going to show those individual pages.
我们只会显示这些单独的页面
But we can enhance with the JavaScript.
但是，我们可以扩展Javascript。
So what happens if you go to the About
所以，当您转到“关于”页面时会发生什么
page is that we leave placeholder sections,
是我们离开部分来保存地方吗
if you like, for Contact, Misc, and Home.
联系人，其他和家庭
And then when you choose one of those,
然后当我们选择一个
we XHR or Fetch-- it's your choice;
我们将根据您的选择执行XHR或Fetch
I chose XHR for reasons that will become
对我来说，我选择XHR，原因如下：
clear-- we XHR or Fetch them in, and we populate them
我们执行XHR或Fetch来获取它并进行资格鉴定
dynamically.
运动学上
And while we're waiting, we show a spinner.
在等待的时候我们看到头晕
All make sense?
可以理解吗？
Good.
好啊
Let's go look at some code.
我们去看看一些符号
Welcome back to the codey bit.
欢迎回到编码部分
I love code.
我喜欢图标
Who doesn't?
不被爱
[LAUGHS]
[笑声]
Yes, now the code.
是的，现在的图标
Well, in fact, as I said over in Theory Corner,
嗯，实际上，正如我在理论角所言
not a lot actually changed inside the router.
我们对路由器的内容没有太大的更改
In fact, most of our changes have happened in the HTML
实际上，大多数更改都发生在HTML中
and in the View.
在视图中
So let's have a look at the HTML.
因此，让我们看一下HTML
So this is what it looks like in the main index.
所以看起来像主要指标
You can see, we've still got our SC.View,
请注意，我们仍然有SC.View
which is the custom element for the view.
它是外观上的专门元素（查看）
But we have now added a visible class
但是我们添加了一个可见的排
for each individual area that's visible.
每个单独的空间都是可见的
In this case, the visible area is home.
在这种情况下，空间是主页
And we have these placeholders, like we talked about in Theory
在理论角我们有保留的地方
Corner for the other views.
对于其他外观
But you'll see, they've got this additional attribute of remote
但您会看到，它具有额外的长期特性
on them, which we're going to pick up in the JavaScript.
我们将使用JavaScript。
While we're also here, it's worth
既然我们在这里，那对我们来说是合适的
noticing that, if we notice that the view is remote,
请注意，外观被认为影响深远
we have a before and an after.
我们之前和之后。
The before is a solid color block,
上一个是纯色块
which its color is inherited from the parents.
它的颜色是从父母那里继承下来的
And the after is this spinner graphic
而且，这是旋转的图纸
that you saw right at the start.
我们首先看到的
Well, how does it all come together?
好吧，您将如何将它们聚集在一起？
Well, for that, we need to look at the view.
要订购它，我们应该看看外观
So our view is pretty much the same as it was.
外观几乎和以前一样
And you'll remember from last time we have something
并记得上次我们有东西
that returns a new promise.
产生新的希望
And we just add the visible class.
并添加可见排名
And we could fade it in, which was fine,
我们可以使其褪色，那很好
because all the content lived inside one page,
因为所有内容都在一页上
but now we got to load in remotely.
但是现在我们必须远程携带它
So what we do is we say, if this is remote--
所以我们说它是否遥远
which looks for that attribute, the remote
哪个在寻找这个属性，
attribute on the view-- and we've not loaded it in before,
远程外观-我们之前没有上传过
load it in.
我们上传他们
So that then says, well, what does the load in code
现在，我们将问，它看起来如何
look like?
下载代码？
Great, glad you asked.
太好了，很高兴你问
Kapow.
卡宝
The code looks like this.
符号看起来像这样
We have, in our case, an XHR.
在这种情况下，我们有XHR。
Now, why not use Fetch?
现在，为什么不使用提取？
That would be a fairly obvious thing to do.
这显然是做什么的
The reason is, you can't Fetch in a document.
原因是，您无法使用“提取”来提取文档
You can XHR in and say the response type is document.
您可以使用XHR并在文档中指示响应类型
But for Fetch, the best you can do
但是对于Fetch来说，最好的办法
is get text and then pass it to a DOMParser, so new DOMParser
是带来脚本并将其传递给DOMParser，因此新的DOMParser
parses text, I think it is, and you tell it it's HTML.
我认为，我将分发这些著作，并告诉他这是HTML。
Not quite as convenient in my view.
我认为这不合适
There's nothing wrong with an XHR, so let's do that.
XHR没有伤害，所以让我们做吧
And so what we do is we create our XHR.
因此，我们要做的是创建XHR，
We set the response type to document.
并证明对文件的回应类型
And then what we do is we look at the URL
然后看URL
that we were trying to get to, and we basically XHR that in.
我们试图达到，然后对我们进行XHR
And whatever we get back from the server side
我们从提供商那里得到的任何东西
is what we're going to work with.
这就是我们要做的
So you'll notice inside there, we query out the visible view.
因此，在内部您会注意到有关可见视图的问题
So for example, if we've requested the About page,
例如，如果我们询问“关于”页面
then the Visible View will be the About content.
可见视图将是“关于”页面
Then what we can do is, you can see we've
然后我们可以做的就是您会看到
got this dot underscore view.
我们的点强调了观点。
And you might be wondering, what's that?
您可能想知道，这是什么？
Well, just look a little bit further up,
好吧，抬头一点
you'll see it's a document fragment.
您会看到它是文档的一部分
So it's a bit of detached DOM that we can work with.
这是一个单独的DOM，我们可以对其进行处理
So we create one of these detached DOM fragments,
因此我们可以创建一个单独的DOM
basically.
基本上
And we populate it with whatever we
并让他有任何资格
manage to pull out from the view that we loaded in remotely.
我们从远程携带的外观中拉出它
So we populate all that, and then you
因此，我们将限定所有这一切，
can see that we append it to this view.
然后您可以看到我们已将其附加到主题
After that, there's just a bit of bookkeeping.
在那之后，几乎没有法规
You remember, I mentioned there's
记得我注意到那里
the before and the after with the spinner on.
旋转转子前后
Well, what we do is we start, as soon as we call
好吧，我们要做的就是我们一开始就开始
into the loadView, we basically say,
loadView，我们将
set a timeout for half a second.
证明超时了半秒钟
If we get to the half a second, we're
如果我们再达到一半
going to show that spinner.
我们将展示转子
If we don't get to half a second, no big deal,
如果我们再没有达到一半，那就没问题了
we'll just show the content.
我们只显示内容
But if we do, you'll see here, we've
但是如果这样做，您会在这里看到
got the showSpinner, which turns on the opacity.
showSpinner，用于操作“不透明度”
And then when the content is actually loaded,
然后，当您下载内容时
we can clear that timeout.
我们可以删除超时
And we can also hide the spinner, which
我们也可以隐藏眩晕，
will cause it to fade out.
它将导致其灭亡
And that will reveal the content behind.
这将显示其背后的内容
So there you go.
所以你可以
Doesn't look like a massive amount
这似乎不算什么
of difference for the user, but it's a huge difference for us.
对于用户而言，这是一个很大的差异，但对我们来说却是一个巨大的差异
because it's allowed us to have progressive enhancement.
因为它为我们提供了逐步的改进
We can now get to those URLs without any JavaScript switched
现在我们可以在哪里获得URL
on.
无需运行任何JavaScript
from there.
从那里
So there you go.
这样我们就成功了
Brilliant stuff.
这是一个天才
Don't forget to check out the live stream.
不要忘记登录直播
If you've not had chance, it's about an hour long.
如果没有机会，大约需要一个小时
In fact, no, I think it was slightly shorter this time.
其实不，我认为这要少一些
Time saving for the win!
这样可以节省您的时间
Cool.
好啊
Don't forget to subscribe.
别忘了注册
And let us know what you think in the comments below.
在下面的注释中让我们知道您的观点
Thank you so much for watching.
非常感谢您的收看
And I'll catch you next time.
我下次见
Who doesn't love a livestream?
谁不喜欢直播？
I love a livestream.
我喜欢直播
You love a livestream.
你喜欢直播
Let's all watch the livestream.
让我们关注直播。
Great hour, funsies.
美好而愉快的时光
Tap ta tap tap, click, click, click.
单击，单击，单击，单击，单击，单击。
I subscribed.
我记录了
[CHEERING] Winning!
[欢呼声]我们成功了